I never dreamed before
（千葉(ちば)）
おーい！ 竜介(りゅうすけ)～ いるか～
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
ムフッ
You're gonna say I'm lying
ボーカルの話 乗るぜー！
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
あいつ…
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
やる気になったのか
(I was made to hit in America)
（千葉）お～い！ 竜介ちゃ～ん
（竜介）フフフ… ご機嫌だな
I was made to hit in America
You are the sun, you are the star
ヘヘ… そいでさ～ ヘヘヘ…
よいしょっ…
(To me, forever)
You are the sun, you are the star
こういうオネーチャンと
お友達になりたいのぉ 僕 ヘヘヘ…
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
Hey! Ryusuke! Are you home?
I'll take that vocalist position!
He's...ready to do it now?
Hey! Ryusuke-chan!
He's feeling good...
And...
I wanna make friends with a girl like this!
"Saito Paper Company"
What do you think?!
（コユキ）どうです！
（斎藤(さいとう)）んー…
That song...What was it?
今の曲…
何？
（コユキ）えっ！
It was "Sunshine" by the Rocket Boys.
ロケットボーイズの
「サンシャイン」…
Let me see your hand.
（斎藤）ちょっと手を見せて
-Nope...Not yet.
-Huh?
ハァ～ まだまだ…
（コユキ）えっ？
You've just started.
（斎藤）
まだ始めたばかりだからねぇ
Fool!
（ペイジ）アホウ！
（コユキ）ぬ～…
（斎藤）コユキ君！
Koyuki-kun!
"25th Annual Sekikawa Hometown Festival"
"Singing Contest"
Tadah!
じゃーん！
"25th Annual Sekikawa Hometown Festival"
"Singing Contest"
A singing contest?
（コユキ）
歌謡… コンテスト？
"25th Annual Sekikawa Hometown Festival"
"Singing Contest"
実は この間の同窓会で
盛り上がっちゃってね
To tell you the truth, things got
exciting at our last class reunion.
My old band members and I
decided to get together again!
昔 組んでたメンバーと—
バンド再結成を決めたんだ！
You mean you're going
to enter the contest?
出るんですか？ コンテスト
Yeah! I registered your name
as a member, too!
コユキ君もメンバーに
登録しておいたから
Huh?! Me, a member?!
えっ！ 僕がメンバー？
（斎藤）
具体的な目標があったほうが
上達は早いんだよ
You'll improve faster
if you have a concrete goal.
俺… まだ始めたばかりだし
But I just got started...
（斎藤）演奏する曲は—
We'll be playing "Follow Me"
by my favorite band, the Rocket Boys.
我が敬愛するロケットボーイズの
「フォロー・ミー」だ
Fool!
（ペイジ）アホウ！
One, two...
（堀内(ほりうち)）ワン！ ツー！
Follow me
Baby, I won't let you leave
if you believe in me
And I always set you free
from all those yesteryears
But you don't know how much
I got believe in you
I was staring at your shoulder shivering
in such a coldest summer breeze
Meanwhile, I wonder why we're here
Look for the line
between love and friends
We'll be twisting ourselves again
I was standing at
the corner on the street
Watching the wheels are turning free
waiting to back up on my-
I'm sorry!
（コユキ）すいません！
（斎藤）ちょっと休もうか
Shall we take a break?
No...I'm fine!
いや… 大丈夫です！
もうすぐ本番だし… 頑張ります！
We have to perform soon...
I'll do my best!
（亀島(かめじま)）コユキ君
Koyuki-kun...You need
a change of pace sometimes.
気分転換も必要だよ
That's right.
（コユキ）すいません…
What are you doing, you blockhead?!
何やってんだ！
このウスノロが～っ！
（コユキ）ハァ… ハァ…
（斎藤）
キックが全然うててねーぞ！
Your kick's no good at all!
よし！ あと５本追加だ！
Okay! Five more laps!
B-but...
そ… そんなぁ…
You, over there...
Don't hang onto the rope.
（監視員）えー そこの少年
コースロープには
つかまらないでください
Raise your pitch! You dumbbell!
（斎藤）ピッチあげろ！
このバカチンがぁ～！
This summer, for some reason,
I learned to do the butterfly kick.
（コユキ）この夏… なぜか俺は
バタフライができるようになった
This fishing hole...
You sure there are fish here?
（千葉）
この釣堀… ホント魚いんの？
Yeah...
-These are Chiba's?
-Yes. That's right.
（カヨ）これって千葉の？
（泉(いずみ)）うん そうだよ
Really? I didn't realize
he listened to this kind of music.
（カヨ）へぇー 千葉って案外
音楽聴いてんだね ふーん
No, ever since he decided to
join the band, he's been studying up.
（泉）バンドやる気になってから
いろいろ研究してるみたいだよ
（カヨ）うーん でも—
But they're all hip hop. You know...
ヒップホップばっかだけど… ね～
フフフッ
まぁ 彼なりに…
Well, he's trying his best.
Say...Have you thought
of a name for the band?
（泉）ねえねえ
バンド名ってもう考えてるの？
Huh?
I guess that's about it.
ま こんなとこか
"MRG (Minami Ryusuke's Group)
Minami Ryusuke Band
R.E.M. (Ryusuke "Eminent" Minami)
Minami Ryusuke & Family
Minami Ryusuke Orchestra"
Why is it you're always...
so self-centered?!
（千葉）なーんで
てめぇは いつもそう—
自己中なんだよ！
I am the one starting up the band.
バンドの発起人は
俺じゃねぇか
Then you decide on the band name, Chiba.
じゃあ千葉が決めろよ
バンドの名前…
Beck!
（千葉）ベック…
（カヨ）え？
Huh?
Let's go with Beck!
「BECK(ベック)」でいこう！
Beck?
ベック… か
Then...Wouldn't Blue Lightning be good?
（千葉）じゃ じゃあ…
「青いイナヅマ」ってのは どうよ
Naked Devils? Or how
about Dream Travelers?
「はだしの悪魔」とかさ～
「夢の旅人
ドリームトラベラーズ」とかさ～
ハハハッ どうこれ？
What do you think?!
Looks like today's contest
will probably be canceled.
これじゃ きょうのコンテストは
中止だな…
"Contest!"
Maybe I should do my homework...
（コユキ）宿題… やろうかな
うわぁっ！
Who's there?!
誰だぁーっ！
Koyuki!
（真帆(まほ)）コユキ～！
（コユキ）えっ？
あっ ま… 真帆ちゃん…
M-Maho-chan...
I'm all wet. Let me in, will you?
（真帆）
ぬれちゃったよ～ ねえ 入れて
Huh?! "Let me in"?
（コユキ）えっ… “入れて”？
I'm sorry for barging in on you.
（真帆）いきなり来て ごめーん！
It's okay, but how did
you know where I lived?
それはいいんだけど…
何で俺の家 知ってんの？
Ryusuke told me when
we passed by the other day.
（真帆）
この前 竜介と通りかかった時
教えてもらったんだ
"Koyuki plays that guitar like
he's trying hard to chase each chord."
“コユキのギターは—”
“コードを追いかけるので
精いっぱいな感じだ”
"There's no feeling."
“フィーリングがない”
"The most important thing is wanting
to convey something to others."
“一番大切なのは—”
“人に何かを伝えようと
思うことなのにな”
Huh? Convey something?
え？ 伝える？
That's what Ryusuke said as
he listened to you playing.
竜介のヤツさぁ—
コユキのギターの音 聴きながら
そういうふうに言ってたよー
Ryusuke-kun said that?
（コユキ）竜介君が…
Ah, that felt good! Thanks, Koyuki!
あー 気持ちよかった～
ありがとう コユキ！
（コユキ）うん…
Sure...
（真帆）ハァ…
Koyuki...Shouldn't you
get ready for the contest?
（真帆）コユキ…
コンテストの用意
したほうがよくない？
Yeah...
"Sekikawa Hometown Festival"
Don't get so tense, Koyuki-kun!
It's only a neighborhood contest!
（斎藤）緊張するなって！
コユキ君！ たかが町内会の
コンテストじゃないか～
あ～ ん～ ウィ～…
You shouldn't be drinking so much.
（堀内）ダメだよ
そんなに飲んじゃ ヘヘッ
Oh, Maho-chan. This is
our drummer, Horiuchi-san.
真帆ちゃん こちらの人が
ドラムの堀内さん
Glad to meet you.
よろしくです
Nice to meet you. I play the drums, yes.
いや～ どーも
ドラム担当してます はい
This is our vocalist and bassist,
Kamejima-san.
（コユキ）こちらが
ボーカルとベースの亀島さん
Kamejima-san!
亀島さん！
K-Kame-yan! Kame-yan!
か… 亀(かめ)や～ん！
亀や～ん！
Wha?! Hic!
え？ ヒック…
Kamejima-san! Can you hear me?
We're going now.
（救急隊員）
亀島さーん 聞こえますねー？
行きますからね よいしょっ
Let's go!
-I'd like you to come too.
-Kamejima-san...
（救急隊員）あなたも
一緒に乗ってください
亀島さん…
Who, me?!
（斎藤）僕？ あ はい…
We're going to win!
優勝する…
Huh?
We've come back together again
after all these years!
数十年ぶりに再結成したんじゃ！
For Kame-yan's sake, we'll win!
亀やんのためにも… 勝つ！
But...Saito-san went
with the ambulance...
でも… 斎藤さんも
付き添いで行っちゃったし…
Then I'll sing!
（真帆）それじゃ 私 歌う！
-Huh?!
You're serious?
（コユキ）マジ？
Yeah!
The prize for this contest is a trip
to Southeast Asia...Quite fancy!
（男性１）
今回の歌謡コンテスト—
東南アジアの旅とは
豪華な副賞ですなぁ
Oh, that. It was a request from the
son of the neighborhood chairman.
（男性２）ああ… あれかぁ
ありゃ 町内会長の息子の
リクエストだ
Oh, really? Isn't the guy
singing right now-
へぇー そうなんですか？
確か今 歌ってるのが…
Yeah. That's the chairman's
good-for-nothing son.
そうそう
会長のところのバカ息子
So you mean the contest is fixed?
じゃ これって
出来レースなんですか？
Probably. Oh, this is
off the record, by the way.
まぁ そんなとこよ
あっ これオフレコってことで…
Oh, boy...
いやはや…
By the way, is Yat-chan well?
ところで ヤッちゃん元気？
Yeah. He's gonna be 24 this year.
ええ もう あいつも
ことしで24ですよ
Oh? No wonder we're getting old.
ほう そりゃ わしらも年とるわ
（男性１・男性２）ハハハハ…
A fixed contest?
出来レース…
（斎藤）ん？ わーぉ！ フフ…
Wow!
You won't know unless you give it a try!
（真帆）そんなの やってみなきゃ
分かんないでしょ！
But...I heard it clearly!
でも 俺 はっきり聞いたもん！
We'll change the minds
of the judges with our music!
私たちの音楽で審査員の気持ちを
変えさせてやる！
That's impossible...
そんなの… 無理だよ
Doesn't it make you mad, Koyuki?!
コユキは悔しくないの？
Sure it does!
But it's how the world works...
悔しいけど！
世の中って…
-We will win!
-Okay! Let's make a bet!
絶対 優勝する！
（斎藤）
よーし 賭けようじゃないか！
フフフ… 負けたほうが—
The loser...has to get naked!
全裸になる！
Yeah! I've been waiting for this!
（男性１）
よっ 待ってました！
So cute...
（男性２）かわいいなー
ヒック…
Koyuki!
（真帆）コユキ！
There are some lines I'm not sure of.
Sing with me, will you?
途中から 歌詞が
分からないところがあるんだ
コユキも歌って！
Follow me
Baby, I won't let you leave
if you believe in me
And I always set you free
from all those yesteryears
（女性）
すごい うまーい！
But you don't know how much
I got believe in you
I was staring at your shoulder shivering
（男性）かわいー！
in such a coldest summer breeze
Meanwhile, I wonder why we're here
Look for the line
between love and friends
We'll be twisting ourselves again
I was standing
at the corner on the street
Watching the wheels are turning free
waiting to back up on my feet
"Emcee" "Judge"
-Reading a line
-between night and day
（田辺(たなべ)）ん？ 田中…？
-I'll be twisting myself
again
あー！ あれは—
That's Tanaka's lucky No. 55 T-shirt!
田中の お気に入りの
55Ｔシャツ！ ヒヒッ
-Follow me
-(Follow me)
-Baby, I won't let you leave
if you believe in me
-(Believe in me)
-And I always set you free
from all those yesteryears
-(Believe in me)
But you don't know how much
-Follow me
-Baby, I won't let you leave
-if you believe in me
-And I always set you free-
Here are the results!
This year's winner is...
（アナウンス）それでは発表します
ことしの優勝は…
(Koyuki!)
(Maho!)
Koyuki...Hurry! Hurry!
（真帆）コユキ 早く早く！
We shouldn't, Maho-chan!
（コユキ）ダメだよ 真帆ちゃん
"Do not use school facilities without-"
Koyuki!
（真帆）コユキ！
Maho...
真帆…
Yay!
（真帆）イェッ！
プハッ ハァ～
Wow! This feels great!
うわー 気持ちいいぞーっ
M-Maho...You're too loud!
What if someone sees?!
（コユキ）ま 真帆 声が大きいよ！
誰かに見られたら…
Full moon sways
Gently in the night of one fine day...
I was fool
Couldn't let myself to go
Even though I feel
The end
Old love affair
Floating like a bird resting her wings
ん… コユキ？
Koyuki?
Here goes!
Full moon sways
Gently in the night of one fine day...
On my way
Looking for a moment with my dear
Full moon waves
Slowly on the surface of the lake
You were there
Smiling in my arms for all those years
-What a fool
-I don't know 'bout tomorrow
-What it's like to be
-Ah...
-I was fool
-Couldn't let myself to go
-Even though I feel
-The end
Old love affair
Floating like a bird resting her wings
You were there
Smiling in my arms for all those years
-What a fool
-I don't know 'bout tomorrow
-What it's like to be
-Ah...
-I was fool
-Couldn't let myself to go
-Even though I feel
-The end
Full moon sways
Gently in the night of one fine day...
You were there
Smiling in my arms for all those years
うん？ うわぁっ！
Observe!
（斎藤）見たまえ！
優勝した若者をぶん殴って—
I punched the lights out of the boy
who won, and took this away!
勝ちとってきたぞ～！
"Southeast Asia Tour"
来週から亀やんと２人で
ツアーに行ってくる
"Southeast Asia Tour"
Next week, Kame-yan and I
are going on a tour!
ムヒー！ ヒヒヒッ
"Southeast Asia Tour"
フフフフ…
夏休みも もう終わりだー！
Summer vacation is over now!
-What?! That's not fair!
（コユキ）えー！ ズルいよー
（真帆）えー！ ズルーい
Don't you owe it to us?!
（コユキ）
俺たちの おかげじゃないの？
（斎藤）フハハ… ワッハハハハ…
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
80 yen in my pocket...
（千葉）
ポケットには80円—
I don't get paid for three more days.
バイトの給料日は ３日後
フッ フフフ… ハハハ…
"Next Episode"
"Hyodo and the Jaguar"
I don't get paid for three more days.
"Next Episode"
"Hyodo and the Jaguar"